本作品由Norm Team倾情奉献
感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为
请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子 字幕:鬼谷子
Compression:GV-Sir Subtitles:GV-Sir
国语音轨提供:晓雪 音轨调整:鬼谷子
Chinese Audio:zy27z Adjust:GV-Sir
敬一部精彩的片子 你们太棒了
To a wonderful film.You were great.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你真浪漫 - 向我的代理 小徒弟干杯
- What a romantic you are. - To the agency and my little protege.
愿主保佑你 多谢老爹
Bless you.Thank you,Daddy.
在贝利兹8年 只懂"胜一胜"?
Eight years at Berlitz,that's what you learn?
他先学"胜" 跟着学"胜一胜"
He learned "chin" the first month and then "chin-chin."
对吗?
Am I right?
我天生迟顿
I can't be clever.
你们做得很好
It was really beautiful,what you guys did.
好极了 你们都很棒
It was beautiful,and you guys are great.
这里的东西很好吃
I love the food here.
我认为影片最精彩之处就在于我们能够摆弄"枪"
The nicest thing about the film is that we get to handle guns.
- 我以前从没那么做过 - 彼得
- I had never done that. - Peter.
- 真不常见 - 什么事?
- Very rare. - What?
- 你好吗? - 本 你好吗?
- How are you? - Oh wow.Ben,how are you?
好极了 先生
Outstanding,sir.
不好意思 这是本·桑德森 这是马克·尼士邦
Oh!Excuse me.Ben Sanderson,Marc Nussbaum.
- 马克·尼士邦 久仰啊 - 你好
- Of course. - How are you?
- 这位是"舒拉" - 两位小姐好
- Sheila. - Ladies.
- 你好 本 - 幸会
- Hi,Ben. - Nice to meet you.
我很欣赏你的杰作 我觉得《猪湾》太棒了
I'm a big fan of your writing.I thought...Bay of Pigs was great.
其实我什么也没写 只写了个剧名 我被解雇了
Actually,I didn't write it,I just got the credit.I was fired.
几年前我跟你通过电话 当时你们都...
Didn't I talk to you a couple of years ago when you both worked
- 在美高梅就职? - 对了 上帝
- at MGM with Laddie? - That's right,by God.
你现在仍替ICM效力?
So are you still at ICM?
- 噢,不,我在三星公司 - 你在三星公司
- No.I'm at TriStar. - You're at TriStar.
- 那么 就请代我向米高问好 - 我会的,我会的
- You'll have to say hello to Mike. - I will.
他已不在那了　可我会逮住他
He's not there anymore,but I'll hunt him down.
- 我有话跟你说 方便吗? - 方便
- Can I talk to you,please? - Yeah,sure.
- 请 - 我很快回来
- Please? - Be right back.
坚守阵地,小伙子.走,去我办公室
Hold the fort,kiddo.I have my own office this way.
- 他到底怎么了? - 他病了
- What is the matter with him? - He's sick.
听着,我帮不了你 你明白吗?
I can't help you anymore.Do you understand?
这是最后一次 我保证 我今晚只是需要一些现金
This is the last time.I promise.I just need some cash tonight.
- 你好 - 我遗失了信用卡
- How are you? - I lost my credit cards.
明天一早还你钱 名誉保证
The money will be on your desk first thing in the morning.
新片如何?据说你请到李察·基尔等大明星
How's the new one coming along?I hear you got Dickie Gere.
- 太棒了 兄弟 - 是啊 阵容鼎盛
- That is great,man. - I got everybody in the movie.
听着 你病了
Look,you're sick.
我身上的钱全在这里
This is all I have in cash.
帮个忙 不要在这里喝
Please,don't drink it in here.
-拜托 -没问题,彼得
- Man. - That's fine,Peter.
明早我会派人还给你
I'll messenger it over to you in the morning.
不 不用还了
No,no.I don't want it.I don't want it.
最好以后别来找我
I think it would be the best thing if you don't contact me again.
彼得?
Peter?
- 你叫什么? - 泰莉
- What's your name? - Terri.
- 泰莉 我请你喝酒 - 别客气
- Terri,I am going to buy you a drink. - I'm OK.Thanks.
不 让我请你喝一杯
No,I am going to buy you a drink.
毕 小姐和你 一人一杯
Bud,please.Buy the lady a drink and another one for you.
我叫本杰明 叫我本就行了
I'm Benjamin.Ben.
本尼·古德曼 就是我 你好性感 棒极了
Benny Goodman,that's me.I think you're sexy.That's right.
看那双迷人的眼睛 性感得象个小猫咪
Look at those eyes.Meow.Sexy like a kitty cat.
我一见倾心
You turn me on
你不高 不矮
You're not too tall You're not too short
不胖
You're not too round
你像只猫 戴帽子的猫
You're like a cat The cat in the hat
看那双迷人的眼睛 向上帝保证
Look at those eyes.Honest to God.
四射的艳光 怎么了?
You're luminescent,baby.What?
- 你喝了一整天的酒了 - 当然
- You've been drinking all day. - Of course.
提到酒 这杯是你的
Speaking of drinks,here is yours.
- 谢谢 - 喝吧
- Thanks. - Down that hatch.
这杯是我的 干杯
And here is mine.Cheers.Come on.
喝 一起喝
There we go.Let's do it to it.
我有个妙不可言的建议
I just thought of an amazing concept.
喝完这杯
What do you say we finish these,
让我们去我在沙滩上的公寓
and we go back to my apartment on the beach!
我播一盒录像带
I'll throw a movie in the VCR...
替你调杯甜酒
and mix you up a gooey blender drink.
- 够浪漫吧? - 嗨 本
- Sound good?Sound sexy? - Hey,Ben.
好吧
OK.
毕 再来一杯
Bud,give me another.
好希望你跟我回家 你娇俏可人
I really wish you'd come home with me.You're so cute.
我床上功夫一流
I'm really good in bed,too.Believe me.
你又香又甜
And you smell great,
秀发如云
and you look great and your hair's great.
不去?好吧
No?OK.
我明天须早起
Look,I've got to wake up early in the morning.
我必须走了 谢谢
I have to go.Thank you.
也许你喝得太多
Maybe you shouldn't drink so much.
也许我呼吸得太多 泰莉
Maybe I shouldn't breathe so much,Terri.
到此为止 我们打烊了
That's it,pal.We're closing up now.
让我喝完这杯
I'm gonna finish this.
你好 "勃起"先生 对我有意吗?
Hey,Mr.Erection,you want a date?
房租20元 你付
The room is 20.You pay for it.
目前的形势...
But only because I think
用投降两个字来形容
that the concept of surrender
可以说是颇为吻合
fits with the big picture right now.
当心点
Hey,get outta the street!
我已搞不清楚 因为被老婆抛弃
I don't remember if I started drinking
所以喝酒
because my wife left me or
还是因为喝酒所以被老婆抛弃
my wife left me 'cause I started drinking.
管他妈的!
Fuck it anyway!
下一位 请
Next,please.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
请稍等 先生
One moment,sir.
请在支票后面签名
Sign the back of the check,please.
- 要签名才能兑现? - 不方便签名吗?
- Can't you just cash it as it is? - Is there a problem?
坦白说 我的手有点颤抖
I'm a little shaky right now.
刚接受过脑部手术
Uh,I had brain surgery.
我先去吃午餐 午餐后
I'll go get some lunch,and then I'll come back
再来提款
and take care of it then.
我要先来杯毡酒
Next I'll have a gin and tonic.
可知现在几点?
Do you know what time it is?
你应该喝咖啡
You should be drinking coffee.
你还年轻
You're a young guy.
我明白 这不关我的事
It's none of my business,
但 你如果能看见自己的情形
but if you could see what I see,
就不会这样对待自己
you wouldn't be doing this to yourself.
我明白你的意思
I understand what you're saying.
感谢你的关怀
I appreciate your concern.
我无意令你不安
It's not my intention to make you uncomfortable.
今天 麻烦你再给我喝一次 以后再也不回来
Please,serve me today,and I'll never come in here again.
再来 你可拒绝招待
If I do,you can 86 me.
废话少说
Stop fucking with me!
我随时都可拒绝招待
I can 86 you anytime I want to.
你怎么喝 我不管
Hey.I don't give a fuck what you do.
这杯酒算入你的账
That one's on the house,son.
地震时你在洛杉矶吗?
Were you in Los Angeles for the earthquake?
- 是的 胆战心惊 - 你损失大吗?
- Yeah,it was pretty scary. - Did you have a lot of damage?
- 一点点 - 你够魅力吗?
- Just a little bit. - Are you desirable?
无可抗拒?
Are you irresistible?
陪我喝酒会有帮助
Maybe if you drank bourbon with me,it would help.
让我吻你 尝到你口中的辣酒 会有帮助
If you kissed me,and I could taste the sting in your mouth,it would help.
你一面散发酒气
If you drank bourbon with me naked,
一面和我干 会有帮助
if you smelled of bourbon as you fucked me,it would help.
我会更敬重你
It would increase my esteem for you
如果你把波本威士忌洒在你的裸体上对我说 喝
if you poured bourbon on your naked body and said to me,"Drink this."
如果你张开双腿 波本威士忌从你的乳房流下来
If you spread your legs and you had bourbon dripping from your breasts
流到你的阴部 并说 喝了它
and your pussy and said,"Drink here"...
那么 我会爱上你
...then I could fall in love with you.
因为当时我有一个目的 清洁你
Because then I would have a purpose:To clean you up.
就能证明自己
And that would prove
不是一无是处
that I'm worth something.
你被我舔干后 可以去跟别人干
I'd lick you clean so that you could go away and fuck someone else.
我们竭诚为顾客服务
Our business is to make our customers happy.
下一位 请
Next,please.
我回来了
I am back.
既有支票 亦可签名
I've got my check,and,baby,I'm ready to sign.
签好了
There.
稳如他妈的泰山 冒昧说句话
Steady as a fucking rock.Excuse my French.
跟我吃晚餐吗?
Want to have dinner with me?
好啊
Yeah.
结尾是怎样?
But what's the back end like?
我们搞妥PA后...
By the time we're through with P and A,uh,
额外的话 就要大约一万五
the "above the line" is gonna take it to about 15.
迪斯尼认为呢?
With something like this,what would Disney think?
- 字条 - 狄拉怎么说?
- Messages. - OK.What did Diller say?
开玩笑而已 我很忙
Listen,I'm very busy.Just kidding.
迟点回你电话
Can I call you back on this?OK.
再见
Ciao for now.
找你来修电话行吗?
Could somebody fix the phones around here?
- 早上好 - 老板在找你
- Good morning. - Mr.Simpson's looking for you.
要立即见你
He wants you to go in as soon as you get...
- 不舒服吗? - 精神很好
- Are you all right? - Outstanding.
但我有个重要的会议
But I have to go to a very important meeting.
会替公司赚数百万
Could make a couple mil for the company.
什么事?
- Ben? - What?
- 你应该马上进去 - 好的
- You should go in there now. - OK.
嗨 本
Hi,Ben.
- 嗨 比尔 - 坐
- Hi,Bill. - Take a seat.
本...
Ben...
不得不请你另谋高就 好吗?
We're gonna let you go,OK?
知道了
OK.
你太慷慨
This is too generous,Bill.
我们很想留用你 但事出无奈
We really liked having you around,but you know how it is.
对不起
I'm sorry.
有什么打算?
Well...What are you gonna do now?
嗯...
Um...
我打算...
I thought,uh...
打算搬去拉斯维加斯
I thought I'd move out to Las Vegas.
远离赌城
我叫尤里·布索夫
My name is Yuri Botsov.
哪国人?
Where you from,Yuri?
肯定不是本国人
You sure don't sound like you come from around these parts.
说得太对了
That is very true.
好眼光 我是立陶宛人
Very good observation.I am from Latvia.
很强硬的国家
Very tough place.
据说是 但在下毫不强硬
I hear this,but I am not a tough man.
诚心来向美国的朋友学习
I am a humble man who is here to learn from my friends in the New World.
- 她一定是尤里的朋友 - 是的!她叫莎拉
- This must be Yuri's friend. - Yes!Sera.
莎拉我的小小意思
Sera is my gift to you all.
她会悉心为各位效劳
You will find her a very willing girl for each of you...
正如我们所安排的一样
just as we arranged.
失陪 大家玩得开心点
So,I have business to attend.Please,enjoy.
要看吗?
Do you wanna watch?
你吓了吗?
Are you scared?
没事
It's all right.
It's OK.
我能令男人大振雄风
I bring out the best in the men who fuck me.
虽不易 但我很在行
It's not easy,but I'm very good.
驾轻就熟 那技巧...
It's amazing.I haven't worked for a really long time,
我可算得上收发自如
and boom,I can just turn on a dime.
男人想让我扮演什么角色都可以
I can just become who they want me to be.
一走进房间 我就心里有数
I walk into that room,I know right away
我会满足他们的欲望
this is their fantasy,and I become it.
这是一种演技 我的拿手好戏
I'm that service.You know?I perform it,and I perform it well.
用身体服务
I'm an equation mostly.
三十分钟 我开价300元
Thirty minutes of my body is...costs $300.
那是入房前的开价
Well,that's just to get into the room.
入房后 改为500 可以议价
It's about $500 after that.We negotiate.
但我提供的是演技
But it's a performance.
完全是演技
It's definitely a performance.
你在这花花世界混
I am very pleased with how you've moved up in the world.
全靠我 混得不错 我很高兴
It is,after all,a glamorous world I showed you.
为什么从洛杉矶溜走?
Why did you leave me in Los Angeles?
因为你奸狡
Because you are sly.
知道这里财路较好
You knew there was more money here in Las Vegas.
你不必怕我
You don't need to fear me,Sera,
你我注定分不开
because we belong together.
对吗?
Don't we?
是啊
Yes.
- 你寂寞吗? - 我寂寞
- Are you lonely? - I am lonely,Yuri.
我也是
So am I.
我们昨晚打电话找你
Janek,we called you last night!
家里没有人
There was no one home.
我们在离拉斯维加斯30英里处
We're 30 miles outside of Las Vegas.
有人在那里见过你
Someone saw him there yesterday.
怎可饶恕?
No,this is the end of it!
尤里明知故犯
Yuri knew what he was doing.
拉斯维加斯
Las.Vegas
那是红灯
That was a red light.
我过马路 你停
I walk,you stop.
- 知错没有? - 是的
- Are you sorry? - Yeah.
很好
Good.
每间房3条毛巾 首块肥皂免费
Three towels in each room and a complimentary bar of soap.
用完后 通知柜台 每块5角
If you run out of soap,you can buy an extra bar.
欢迎使用泳池 但安全自负
Feel free to use our pool,but use it at your own risk.
- 每间房3条毛巾 - 有空房吗?
- There are three towels in your room. - Hi,do you have vacancies?
有 请等一下
We do.I'll be with you in a minute.
床单我们供应 房租每晚29元
Linens are provided for you.Rooms are $29 a night.
每周一付钱 女佣服务另计
You pay at the beginning of each week.Maid service is optional...
女佣服务另计 每日3.5元
Maid service is optional.It costs $3.50 a day.
欢迎使用泳池 但安全自负
Feel free to use the pool,but use it at your own risk.
泳池没救生员
We don't have a lifeguard.
禁止带儿童 宠物 晚上11点后禁止访客入内
No kids,no pets and no guests after 11:00 at night.
你的房内有3条毛巾
You've been provided with three towels.
我希望你走时 房里仍有3条毛巾
We expect when you check out there will still be three towels.
首块肥皂免费
There's a complimentary bar of soap.
我入房时 他躺在床上
I walked into the room,and he was lying on the bed.
头枕着双臂
He had his arms behind his head,
浑身毛烘烘
and there was just hair everywhere.
十分肥胖
He was really,really fat.
私处在勃起 很大
He had a large erection.
我记得 他对自己的大阳具...
I remember,he was so proud of his...
相当自豪
...large erection.
之后我,嗯...
And I,uh...
我问"钱在哪里" 他指一指衣柜
I asked him where my money was,and he pointed to the dresser.
然后我问"要什么姿势"
And then I asked him what he wanted,
他说"躺下 我在上"
and he said,"Lie down,I'm on top."
他于是朝着我用力撞击起来
He started pounding me really hard.
我咬牙强忍 才没哭出来
I had to bite my tongue to keep from crying.
他撞击了一会儿 我正想起来
He did that for a while,and then I started to get up.
却被他推倒 并且抓住我的头发
He pushed me back down,and he held my hair.
他抓着我的头发 同时把阳具塞入我口中
He was pulling it,and he stuck his penis in my mouth.
我又想起身 他说
I tried to get up again,and he said,
"别动 我要在你脸上射精"
"Stay there,baby,I'm gonna come on your face."
他真的射了
So he did.
并且把精液涂满我的脸和头发
Then he rubbed his semen all over my face and in my hair.
后来,嗯...
And,uh...
跟着 踢我下床 叫我走
Then he kicked me off the bed and told me to leave.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 在做生意? - 什么意思?我在走路
- Are you working? - What do you mean?I'm walking.
等一等
Just wait one second.
好棒的屁股?
Great ass!
- 喝点吗? - 喝酒驾车 不违法?
- Want some? - Isn't it illegal to drink and drive?
你真幽默
That's pretty funny.
我付250元给你干 愿意吗?
I wonder if you'll take $250 to fuck me?
你在我房间逗留1小时
That is,if you'll come to my room for one hour,
我付你500元
I will give you $500.
- 你醉得不行了 - 不醉
- You're pretty drunk. - Not really.
我住在全年旅馆 不远
My room's not far.It's The Whole Year Inn.
我们可驾车或徒步
You could drive with me if you want or we could walk.
或坐的士我付钱
Or I could give you cab fare.
- 先上车 - 你要什么都可以
- In the car. - Whatever you want.
上车后再付钱给我
Why don't you give me the money in the car?
我叫本
I'm Ben.
我叫莎拉
I'm Sera.
莎拉 有个H的?
Sarah with an "H"?
有个E的 S-E-R-A
With an "E." S-e-r-a.
还不开车?
You wanna start the engine?
哇
Wow.
这屋子貌似更需要酒
What this room needs is more booze.
- 可以用洗手间吗? - 请便
- Mind if I use the bathroom? - Of course.
喝一杯吗?我要喝一杯
Want a drink?I'm having one.
好的 如果你愿意的话 我想要一杯特奎拉酒
Sure.I'll have a shot of tequila,if you can spare it.
酒来了
Your drink's here.
付500元 你怎样都可以
For 500 bucks,you can do pretty much whatever you want.
- 你可以爆菊花 - 有没有搞错?
- You can fuck my ass. - Oh,my God.
- 你可以射在我的脸上 - 哇!
- You can come on my face. - Whoa!
随你喜欢
Whatever you want to do.
但别沾上我的头发
Just keep it out of my hair.
- 好的 - 我刚洗过
- OK. - I just washed it.
"只因早上我双脚太大"
<i>Just because my feet Were too big in the morning</i>
"只因我记得你母亲的名字"
<i>Just because I can't remember Your mother's name</i>
"只因我放八爪鱼在床上"
<i>Just because I put the octopus In the bed</i>
"只因为...因为 因为...因为比尔考斯比"
<i>Just because,because Because,because Bill Cosby</i>
现在想干吗?
You wanna fuck now?
也许先喝点酒 还要特奎拉吗?
Maybe something to drink first.More tequila?
随便你
Whatever.
好了 好了
OK.OK.OK.
怎么了?喝得太醉 没有高潮了?
What's the story?Are you too drunk to come?
有没有 无所谓
I don't care about any of that.
还有时间 你可以得到更多的钱
There's time left.You can have more money.
酒随便你喝
You can drink all you want.
只是别走 我就想要你留下
Just stay.That's what I want.
说说话 或者听我说
I want you to talk or listen.
只要你别走
Just stay.
那么 名字带N的本...
So,Ben with an "N,"
来拉斯维加斯干什么?
what brings you to Las Vegas?
业务会议?
Business convention?
不是
No.
我来是为了喝酒寻死
I came here to drink myself to death.
变卖了一切财物
Cashed in all my money,
偿还了信用卡
paid my AMEX card,
明天卖车
gonna sell the car tomorrow.
你估计要多久...
How long is it gonna take for you to
才能喝死?
Drink yourself to death?
我估计大约四星期
I think about four weeks.
我也不确定,我想差不多吧
I don't know for sure,but I think.
我每天可以用250到300元
I got enough for about 250,$300 a day.
应该够
That should do it.
我算什么?奢侈品?
What am I?A luxury?
是的
Yes.
而你这奢侈品已经到点了
You're a luxury,and your meter just ran out.
不错的手表
That's a nice watch.
- 喜欢吗? - 是的
- You do like it? - Yes.
不妨多聊聊
You can talk a little bit more.
我没特别的去处
I don't have to be anywhere.
拜托!聊吧
Come on,talk.
在洛杉矶
In LA...
我经常忘记在开店前买酒
...I kept running out of booze and the store would be closed
因为我总忘记看表
because I forget to look at my watch.
我以前...我以前住在洛杉矶
I used to...I used to live in LA.
- 是吗? - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
现在已经不在那里住了
But I don't anymore.
我的艰难日子已成过去
I think the tough times are finally behind me.
将来仍会有困难 但...
There'll always be bad things,but...
生活会好过点
...my life is good.
我已经满足
It is as I want it to be.
很好
It's good.
与你一起很好
It's good being here with you.
该死
Shit.
嗨 比尔 你好
Hey,Bill.How are you?
整晚就只赚这一点?
Is this a full night's work?
很对不起
I'm really sorry.
昨晚生意淡 我拉不到客
It was such a slow night,and I couldn't score.
你以为你是谁?
What do you think?
你自以为是好菜坞大道上16岁的姑娘?
You're just a 16-year-old girl on Hollywood Boulevard?
你是这么想的?你想耍我?
Is that what you think?Is that what you play?
没有
No.
拿着
Here.
动手吧
Go ahead.
我可以宰掉你 莎拉
I could kill you,Sera.
我可以宰掉你
I could kill you.
你今晚接客 交钱来
You work tonight,and you bring me the money.
不管多晚
It doesn't matter how late.
我会
I will.
是的 他割过我好几次
Yeah,he cut me a couple of times.
他总向保证 不割脸部
He'd always say,"Never on the face."
于是割这里
So,he cut me right here.
割完就哭
He cried...
我替他难过
...and I felt sorry for him.
他认为我做了坏事
Well,in his mind,I'd done something bad,
但我认为自己没有
but in my mind I hadn't done anything bad.
他有点疑神疑鬼
He's kind of paranoid.
这红宝石戒指是我的吉祥物
This ring is a ruby.It's my lucky ring.
这手表是足金的 并非镀金
This watch is real gold.It's not plated.
是真的 沉甸甸
It's the real thing.Feel how heavy it is.
- 手表加戒指 3千元 - 1千
- These rings,$3,000. - One thousand.
一千 看 物超所值啊
One thousand?Look what you're getting.
我这红宝石吉祥戒指 多漂亮
It's a ruby.It's my lucky ring.It's a beautiful thing.
一并变卖 两千
I can put that in.Two thousand dollars.
- 我最高只出一千 - 但我加上戒指
- I can't give you more than a thousand. - But I just added the ring.
- 人造红宝石戒指 - 看...
- Synthetic ruby. - Look...
有何贵干?
What can I do for you?
500元
Five hundred.
500元变卖93年劳力士日历表
Five hundred dollars for a '93 Rolex Daytona.
卖
I'll do it.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 你好吗? - 不错 谢谢
- How are you doin'? - I'm doing fine,thank you.
来开会?
Are you here for the convention?
- 想不到一眼就被人看出 - 哦 不会吧
- I didn't think I was that obvious. - Oh,no.
- 瞎猜而已 - 我叫保罗
- It was just a wild guess. - My name's Paul,honey.
- 伏特加七喜 - 小姐呢?
- Vodka Seven. - And for the lady?
- 多喝一杯吗? - 好
- Are you ready for another one? - Sure.
- 要被玛特嘉烈特 - 好品味
- I'll have a margarita. - Good choice.
那么 你一个人吗?
So are you alone?
还是利用我来让别人妒忌?
Or are you just using me to make someone else jealous?
一个人 我是一个人
Alone.I'm here alone.
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Cheers.
你住哪?
Where are you staying?
就住这酒店里 怎么了?
Right here at the hotel.Why?
你可能想要女伴
I thought you might be looking for a date.
女伴?你是妓女?
"A date"?What are you,a hooker?
你说女伴到底是什么意思?
What exactly do you mean by a date?
我是有妻室之人
I got a wife waiting for me at home.
- 来这里只为开会几分钟 - 对不起 我误会了
- I just came over to talk. - I'm sorry.I guess I misunderstood.
- 你是的 - 小声一点好吗?
- I guess you did. - Just keep your voice down.
我不会再打扰你
I won't bother you again.
喝多杯吧 我请
Here,have another one on me.
有没搞错?
Christ.
你今晚应休息
Maybe you should give it a miss for tonight.
我不知道 只是...
I don't know,it's just...
我的确喜欢这个家伙 但我从未对...
I really like this guy.I've neverfelt anything
其他嫖客有过感觉
for anyone I've ever been with,as a trick,you know?And it's...
事情来得莫名其妙 我觉得种类混淆
It's weird.I feel kind of confused about it.
我们仅仅相处了一晚
We were with each other only one night,
但是 我觉得象是某种关系
but I felt like the relationship...
我觉得好象有种关系形成了
I felt like there was a relationship being formed.
有点害怕
I was kind of scared.
不
No?
我想我不应该再见他
I don't think I should see him again.
可是我在找他
But I look for him.
昨晚我出去了 我就是在找他
I went out last night.I was looking for him.
嗨
Hi.
你的车呢?
So where's your car?
今早卖掉了
I sold it this morning.
从此得坐计程车
I'm gonna take cabs from now on.
今晚有什么节目?付我500元看你睡觉?
What's it tonight?Another 500 to watch you sleep?
- 怎么了? - 我今晚在找你
- What's up? - I was looking for you tonight.
不知你有没有男友
I don't know if you have a boyfriend,
或女友
or a girlfriend,
但你有空的话
but if you have some free time,
你我或许可以一起吃晚餐
I thought maybe we could get some dinner.
你说真的吗?
Are you serious?
哦 我想你知道我是认真的
Oh...I think you know I'm serious.
如果你愿意的话 我会付你钱
I'll pay you if you like,
我只是想见见你
but I just want to see you.
不 我不能跟你吃饭
No,I can't have dinner with you.
可以吃排骨
We could get prime rib.
排骨有特价 2.99元
They've got it on sale for $2.99.
裙子好看
I love that dress.
尤里 我今晚生意很好
Yuri,I had a really good night.
收入终于有改善
I think things are finally picking up.
我们赚到好多钱 看
We made so much money.Look.
过来
Come here.
听 听到了吗?
Now,listen.Do you hear?
他们在谈论我呢
They're talking about me.
听到了吗?
Do you hear?
尤里 你没事吧?
Are you all right?
你走吧
Get out.
再别回来 我不想再见到你
Do not come back here.I'll not see you again.
你还想请我吃饭吗?
Do you still wanna have dinner?
是的
Yes.
我撒了太多盐
I think I put too much salt on it.
- 那不好 - 不 那很好
- It's not good. - No,it's good.
- 你怎么变成酒徒呢? - 我怎么变成酒徒?
- Why are you a drunk? - Why am I a drunk?
你真想知道?
Is that really what you want to ask me?
是啊
Yes.
这是你我首次约会 抑或最后一次约会
Then this is our first date or our last.
至今我仍不敢肯定
Until now,I wasn't sure it was either.
首次
First.
首次约会
It's our first.
我只想知道
I just wanna know.
你为什么寻死?
Why are you killing yourself?
有趣的措辞
Interesting choice of words.
我记不起 我只想死
I don't remember.I just know that I want to.
你是说 喝酒是寻死之道?
Is your drinking a way to kill yourself?
- 或者 寻死是喝酒之道 - 好聪明
- Or killing myself is a way to drink. - Very clever.
说吧
Shoot.
能再给一份吗?
Can I have another one?
你在想什么?生我的气?
What are you thinking?Are you angry?
没有
No.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
- 我很开心 - 本
- I had the most wonderful... - Ben.
来我家过夜好吗?
Why don't you stay at my place tonight?
我是说 你看 你都醉成这个样子了
I mean,look,you're pretty drunk.
- 我喜欢你 信任你 - 哇 太出人意料了 莎拉
- I like you.I trust you. - Wow.That's astonishing,Sera.
我不忍见你住那低级旅馆
I hate to think of you in that cheesy motel.
令你好受点 我明天搬进大酒店
I'll move to a real smart hotel tomorrow if it makes you feel better.
谈谈明天吧 你有什么打算?
Let's talk about tomorrow.Do you want to do something?
好 今晚在我家谈
We'll talk about it tonight at my place.
我在床上不太行
I'm not much good in the sack.
与上床无关
Ben,it's not about sex.
你在沙发椅睡
I'll make you up a bed on the sofa.
我们谈到深夜 睡到日上三竿
We'll talk till late.We'll sleep till late.
我没有人管
As you know,I am my own boss.
来我家吧
Do it,Ben.
好吧
OK.
我去
I'll do it.
这是天使的家
This is the home of an angel.
- 你没事吧? - 当然没事
- Are you OK? - Of course.Wow.
你看起来真美
You look extremely beautiful.
是吗?
I do?
我是说 这确实不可思议
I mean,it's really weird because,um...
你知道的...
...you know,
只是觉得这件事 进展得太快了
it's just like this thing's happening really quickly.
真有些莫名其妙
I just don't know what's going on.
就在我见到他的一瞬间 就自报名字
Just the second I met him,and the way I said my name.
我脱口说出 "嗨 我叫莎拉" 我通常不会
I just said,"Hi,my name's Sera," and that's not what I do.
只是...这一切突如其来
And it's just...It's all happening really quickly.
我只是觉得我俩...我俩一见如故
I just felt like we were...we've been together for a long time.
跟他一起很开心
Itjust felt so easy,
觉得...
and I felt like,um...
回复自我
I felt like I was me.
觉得不是在
I didn't feel like I was...
不是在伪装别人
...trying to be somebody else.
旅馆的租金什么时候要交?
When is your rent coming up at the motel?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我认为 我应该把所有行李搬来
I think you should go and bring all your stuff over here.
莎拉
Sera.
- 莎拉 你疯了吗? - 怎么了?
- Sera,you are crazy. - So?
你不认为跟一个酒鬼在一起生活很乏味吗?
Don't you think you'll get a little bored living with a drunk?
- 可我希望这样 - 你还没见过更糟的呢
- That's what I want. - You haven't seen the worst of it.
最近这几天 我一直很有节制
These last few days,I've been very controlled.
我打翻东西 不断呕吐
I knock things over and throw up all the time.
现在 我感觉好多了
Right now,I feel really good.
你就像解药 里面掺着酒 让我保持平衡
You're like an antidote that mixes with the liquor and keeps me in balance.
但这种情况不会长的
But that won't last forever.
那好吧
OK.
好了 你回去你的旅馆
All right,you go back to your motel.
我继续过我一个人富有魅力的生活
I'll go back to my glamorous life of being alone.
我回家的唯一理由是回来用漱口剂...
The only thing I have to come home to is a bottle of mouthwash...
除去嘴巴的那种味道
to take the taste of come out of my mouth.
我一个人呆够了
I'm tired of being alone.
厌烦透了
That's what I'm tired of.
你不喜欢我 本?
Don't you like me,Ben?
莎拉
Sera...
你有所不知...不 瞧? 不
What you don't understand is...No.See?No.
什么?
What?
永远不要...
You can never,never
制止我喝酒
ask me to stop drinking.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
我明白
I do.
真的明白
I really do.
是的 我的确为你神魂颠倒
Yes,I'm nuts about you.
知道吗?
OK?
我们不知道...
We didn't know...
- 应不应该报警 - 他在这里已经半小时了
- whether to call the police. - He has been here about half an hour.
- 我知道... - 虽然米奇见过你俩一起
- I know that... - Mickey had seen you two together.
但我不可能开门 因为摸不清底细
I was not about to open the door.I don't know who,I don't know where,
我什么都摸不清 这年头...
I don't know what,I don't know whatever these days.
- 他是我朋友 - 不好意思
- He's my friend. - I'm sorry.
大概喝多了一点酒
He must have had a little too much to drink.
我要他按密码 但他办不到
That's why I had him patch the key code.Because he's not gonna do it.
我会扶他进去 谢谢
I'll help him inside.Thank you so much.
- 抱歉打扰你们 - 没事
- I'm so sorry to bother you. - No trouble.
要帮忙的话 只管打电话给我
You just give me a call if you need any help.
本 醒一醒好吗?
Ben,can you wake up?
嗨
Hi.
我们要进屋去 我有礼物给你
We gotta go inside,but I have some presents for you.
起来
Up we go.
- 起来 - 这位是范太太
- Here we go. - This is Mrs.Van Houten.
他叫本
This is Ben.
你好
Outstanding,sir.
行 进去吧
All right.Here we go.
- 可以应付吗? - 可以
- You're OK? - I'm fine.
- 好 - 很抱歉打扰你
- Good. - I'm so sorry to bother you.
- 谢谢你能体谅 - 没事
- Thank you for being so nice. - Sure.
- 好 - 再见
- All right. - Bye-bye.
对不起 我失去了知觉
Sorry.I was miles away.
礼物
The gifts.
莎拉
Sera.
我喜欢这个名字
I love that name.
S-e-r-a.
在我们继续下去之前 我有话想说 可以吗?
Before we proceed onwards,there's something I have to say,OK?
好的
OK.
我终于来到你的家中
I've come this far.Here I am,in your house.
- 请让我付本月的租金 - 不必 为什么?
- Let me pay this month's rent. - No.Why?
因为...
Because...
因为那样对我比较好 可以吗?
Because it's better for me that way,OK?
好的
OK.
可以坦白说
I'll tell you right now,
我已爱上你
I'm in love with you.
但我无意因自己颓废
But,be that as it may,I am not here
成为你生活上的负担
to force my twisted soul into your life.
我明白
I know that.
你我都知道我是酒鬼
We both know I'm a drunk.
你是妓女
And I know you're a hooker.
对你这方面 我对此
I hope you understand that I'm a person
毫不介意
who is totally at ease with this,
并不是我置之度外 漠不关心
which is not to say that I'm indifferent or I don't care.
我关心
I do.
我只是信赖 接受你的抉择
It simply means I trust and accept your judgment.
我本来顾虑这方面
I was really worried about how that would be,
现在放心了
but now I'm not.
但在这里租屋
But you should know that included with the rent around here
免费奉送性服务
is a complimentary blowjob.
是的
Yes.
我想迟早我们要云雨的
I suppose sooner or later we ought to fuck.
不管你怎么说
Whatever that means.
- 开礼物看看 - 礼物
- Open your presents. - Presents!
好了
OK.All right.
先开这个
Open this one first.
真好看
Very nice.
很适合配我的西装
This should go very nicely with my suit,
那套西装是我从旅馆带来的...
which,by the way,is the only item of clothing
唯一行李
I brought over from the motel with me.
对 行李箱空空如也
Oh,right.The suitcase was clinking.
你的衣服呢?
What did you do with your clothes?
都扔掉 或者有点浪费
I threw them out,which was perhaps immoral,
但我总算干干净净来这里
but I wanted to come to you clean,so to speak.
我们应去买衣服 买一条牛仔裤
Thought we'd go shopping for a pair ofjeans
45条内裤 每天扔一条
and 45 pairs of underwear,and just throw one out each day.
说得好 酒继续喝
That's nice talk,Ben.Keep drinking.
你的嘴 除了喷酒气 流口水外
Between the 101-proof breath and the occasional drool,
还有风趣谈吐
some interesting words fall from your mouth.
我找到了红颜知己
It looks like I'm with the right girl.
你肯买这个给我 的确难得
I'm very impressed you would buy this for me.
现在就用来装酒
I'm gonna fill it right now.
今晚想赌钱吗?
Do you want to go gambling tonight?
或许可以小试手气
I was thinking we could go and just play for a few hours.
我没考虑过
I hadn't planned to gamble,
但如果把大部分的钱交给你保管
but if you could keep the bulk of my money,
玩几百块 无所谓
I could safely blow a couple hundred bucks.
给你钱 有快感
Giving you money makes me want to come.
随时可以有
Then come.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
- 我有13点 - 要牌?
- You got a 13. - Hit me.
- 等等 她有7点 - 我不知道 你作主吧
- Wait.She's got a seven. - I don't know.You tell me.
- 发牌 - 爆了 不要紧
- Hit. - I'm busted.That's all right.
牌好 这趟你吃定
You got it.You can do it.
等一等 当真?
Wait a minute!Really?Oh,man!
- 什么? - 他没事
- What? - He's OK.
要点酒吗?
Do you want anything?
要杯茄汁伏特加 行吗?
Yeah,maybe a Bloody Mary.Can you make that?
什么?
What?
什么?不!不!
What?No!No!
去你妈的?蠢货
Fuck you!Fuck!You fucker!
你不能这样?
That boy is...You can'tjudge me!
我是他老子!
You!I am his father!
起来?
Get up!
走吧
Let's go,guys.
本?
Ben?
- 觉得怎样? - 很好
- How are you? - Very well.
想不到要再问你
I never expected to have to ask this again,
今晚发生了什么事?
but how did our evening go?
我记得我们进了赌场
I remember getting to the casino.
记得和你接吻 好开心
And I remember kissing you.That was really nice.
然后正玩着21点 然后警卫来了
And playing blackjack,and then security came.
跟着 一片空白 发生了什么事?
But after that,everything's a blank.What happened?
警卫本来打算把你扔出去
They wanted to carry you out and dump you onto the street,
被我说服 准我扶你走
but I talked them into letting me walk you out.
不容易啊
That's impressive.
怎么说服他们?
How did you do that?
我告诉他们你是个酒鬼
I told them that you were an alcoholic...
我会送你回家
...and that I would take you home...
今后我们再也不到那去了
...and that we would never go in there ever again.
我们?
"We"?
是的 我们
Yes,we.
好神奇
That's amazing.
你是谁?
What are you?
你是我醉乡中的天使下凡来看我?
Some sort of angel visiting me from one of my drunk fantasies?
你怎可能这样好?
How can you be so good?
我不知你说什么
I don't know what you're saying.
我只是在利用你
I'm just using you.
需要你
I need you.
别再提 只字别提
Can we not talk about it anymore?Not a word.
你睡觉吧
You go back to sleep,
我去买早餐
and I'll go out and get us some breakfast.
- 小心点 - 别担心
- Will you be careful? - Don't worry.
我今晚要出去做
Ben,I'm working tonight.
我知道
I know.
我说个不休 因为你听不进去
I fuckin' talk all the time because you never fuckin' listen to me!
- 去死吧 - 他妈的闭嘴
- So fuck you! - Shut the fuck up.
一杯啤酒 两份"神风" 麻烦
I'd like a beer and a double Kamikaze,please.
酒吧台不可以踢 只可以倚
We mustn't kick the bar.We lean into the bar.
身体斜倚扶手
Just lean into the railing.
那不是真正的酒鬼 那是一种廉价的酒鬼
It's not vino veritas.It's en vino veritas.
你他妈的在跟谁说话?
Who the fuck are you talking to?
酒糟鼻子 手持弹弓的小矮人
Little brown-nosed gnomes with a slingshot.
廉价的酒鬼 廉价的酒鬼
en vino veritas.en vino veritas.
- 就是为了醉酒 - 斜倚扶手?
- To be in drunk. - Lean into the bar?
你斜倚扶手
You lean into the bar.
我被男友闷得要死
Listen,my boyfriend over there is really boring the shit out of me
肯请我喝杯酒吗?
and I was wondering if you would buy me a drink?
我请她喝酒 介意吗?
Do you mind if I buy her a drink?
- 你对她怎样 我不管 - 我要拉姆酒可乐
- I don't care what you do with her. - I'll have a rum and Coke,please.
酒保 拉姆酒可乐
Barman,a rum and Coke.
到你家暂住行吗?
Can I stay with you for a while?
搬进我家?有点太突然吧?
You mean move in with me?Isn't this a bit sudden?
我没什么行李
I don't have a lot of things.
我的太太会不高兴
I don't think my wife would dig it very much.
你我找个旅馆 干个天昏地暗 如何?
Then maybe we should just go to a motel and fuck all day.
我可以替你吹箫
I could suck you like this.
跟你干 肯定其乐无穷
I'm sure fucking you would be wonderful,
但我没法随便跟人亲热
but it's almost impossible for me to imagine being with someone else.
听着 混蛋 我不会眼巴巴的坐在这里
Now listen,asshole,I'm notjust gonna sit here
任由她吮你的耳朵
and watch her suck on your ear!
你他妈的闭嘴?
Shut the fuck up!
对不起
I am sorry,
我只想和她共度几小时
but she and I have decided to spend a few hours together
在旅馆里
in a motel.
之后 一起吃鱼子酱
And after that,caviar.
哇!
Woo!
等我一下 宝贝!
Baby,wait up!
你身手不凡
You're quite a fighter.
拿去
Here.
听着 虽然这听起来有些傻...
Listen,this may sound silly,
但是我不得不请你离开
but I have to ask you to leave.
这是这里的规矩
It's what we do around here when there's a fight.
男厕在后面
The men's room is around the back.
性感 真性感
Sexy,sexy.
- 我回来了 - 米基
- I'm back. - Mickey!
嘣!
Boo!
天啊
Oh,my God.
- 吓你一跳? - 什么事了?
- Did I scare you? - What happened?
跟人打架了?
Fuck,Ben.Did you get in a fight?
你说过自己不动粗
I thought you said you didn't fight.
觉得怎样?
How do you feel?
觉得天旋旋 地转转
Like the kling-klang king of the rim-ram room.
你去了酒吧?
Did you stop at a bar?
你当着蠢人的面说蠢话了?
Did you say something stupid to somebody stupid?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
我只是维护一个苦命女孩的清白
I was defending the honor of some poor wayward maiden.
我相信你会这么做
I bet you were.
去洗个澡 换件衣服
Why don't you go take a shower and put on your other shirt?
我们去给你买些新衣服
Then we'll go shopping and buy you some new clothes.
这件衣服不太吉利
I think this shirt is unlucky.
怎会?
Not at all.
你的血很好吃
Your blood tastes good.
我买了些鸡蛋
Hey,we got eggs.
我曾幻想自己跳西班牙舞
I always had a fantasy of being a flamenco dancer.
我认为你好看
I think you look great.
打个蝴蝶结
We'll just get you a bow tie,
就像21点的庄家
and then you can be one of those blackjack dealers.
- 对不对? - 但他们是必须打蝴蝶结的
- All right? - They wear it because they have to.
而我是自愿的
I'll wear it because I want to,
所以我和他们不同
which will make me look different.
本
Ben.
我们去喝东西
Let's get a drink!
- 什么东西? - 什么?
- What is that? - What?
天啊!从你耳朵取出来的
Holy cow.It came out of your ear!
我没机会写卡片...
I didn't have time to write you a card,
因为你整天都缠着我...
with you breathing down my neck all day,
只好有礼物而无卡片
so you'll just have to wing it,baby.
打开
Open it.
你的颜色
They're your color.
你每次只应戴一只
I think you should wear one of them at a time.
配一只其他的耳环
One of these and one of your other ones.
我本打算只买一只
I was gonna buy you just one,
但大概不可
but I didn't think it would fly.
护士一只耳环 不可当礼物
Nurse!As a gift,I mean.Aah!
我今晚就戴
I'll wear them tonight.
只戴一只
One of them.
今晚
Tonight.
就戴
Put it on.
戴不上
I can't get it.
我帮你戴
I'll help you.
倘若在公寓内 某位仁兄...
You'll be able to feel it,sharp and hot under your ear,
打你的脸 按在枕头上
as one of the brothers is putting your head face down
你会觉得耳后有点刺痛
into one of the penthouse pillows.
本 等一下
Ben,wait!
也许你应等一下
Maybe you should wait.
为什么?
Why?
看得出 她真的想要你等
You can tell.She really wants you to.
也许我应该跟在你身边
Maybe I should follow you around
问你的客人跟你睡觉是怎样的
and ask one of your tricks what it's like to sleep with you.
他们不会知道的
They wouldn't know.
你应该问我
Maybe you should ask me sometime.
我乐意示范
Be happy to show you.
我三点左右回来
I'm gonna be home around 3:00.
如果你回来 我们就可以一起看电视什么的
If you're back,we could watch some TV or something.
我的意思是 希望回来能见到你
What I'm saying is that I hope you're back when I get home.
小心
Be careful.
你也小心
You be careful,too.
我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you.
我知道沙漠中有个很酷的地方
I know this really cool place in the desert.
我们可以去散心
We could go away for a couple days.
好啊
Yeah.
我想去
I'd like that.
我会做鬼脸
I make comic faces and
倒立 变低腰 倒转向你微笑
stand on my head and grin at you between my legs and...
我会说很多笑话
...I know loads ofjokes.
我们没戏了 是吗?
Wouldn't stand a chance,would I?
你的确劝过我去找个女友
You did tell me I ought to find myself a girl.
我喜欢跟你这样
I like it here with you.
咱们再呆一会儿吧
Let's stay for a while.
- 需要个搅拌器? - 几时要?
- Need a mix master. - What?
把所有的酒混起来
Just sort of take everything and blend it all together.
脱下
Take this off.
- 进房吧 - 好
- Let's go inside. - All right.
我去拿我的酒
I'm gonna get my drinky.
天啊有受伤吗?
Oh,my God!Are you OK?
流血了 等一等
You're bleeding.Wait.Hold it.
- 有玻璃碎片 - 我像个仙人球!
- There's glass in here. - I'm like a prickly pear!
- 我是个仙人球! - 你先进去
- I'm a prickly pear! - Go inside.
- 我想收拾玻璃 - 你进去 我来收拾
- I wanna clean up the glass. - Go inside.I'll take care of it.
肯定?
Are you sure?
好吧
All right.
- 你们没事吧? - 我们很好
- Everybody OK? - We're fine.
真抱歉 我们会赔偿桌子的...
I'm so sorry.We'll pay for the table,
- 我会收拾干净的 - 不要紧
- and I'll clean this up. - Don't worry.
你似乎见惯不怪
You seem prepared for accidents.
我们经常碰到酒鬼
We get a lot of screw-ups here.
你们两人把话和酒带到屋里去
You two take your loud talk and your liquor to your room.
明天一早退房
You check out first thing tomorrow.
我不想再看到你们任何一个
I don't want to see either of you here ever again.
不用担心赔偿的事
Don't you worry about paying for anything.
不用担心你的小手会被玻璃割到
And don't you worry about cutting your little hands on the glass.
就放在那别管了
Let's just leave it at that.
明早见
See you in the morning.
莎拉
Sera?
本 我在这里
I'm in here,Ben.
我买了些米饭
I bought some plain rice.
你现在可能听不进去
You probably don't want to hear it right now,but...
但应该吃点饭
I think it's something that you could eat.
饿的话叫我 好吗?
If you get hungry,will you let me know?
我可以吃饭了
I think I'm ready for rice.
我想让你去看医生
I want you to see a doctor.
莎拉
Sera.
我不会去看医生的
I'm not gonna see a doctor.
我或许应该搬到酒店去住
Maybe it's time I moved to a hotel.
去干嘛?
And do what?
在房里面腐烂而死
Rot away in a room?
我们不谈这个
We're not gonna talk about that.
去你的 现在不谈这个
Fuck you.We're not gonna talk about that.
你要住在这里
You're staying here.
别到旅馆去
You're not going to any motel.
这是你唯一能为我做的事 就这一件事
It's just one thing you can do for me.Just one thing.
就这点要求
That's all I ask.
我给了你多少自由
I've given you gallons of free will.
就要你为我做这么一件事!
You can do this one thing for me!
我现在要去干活了
I have to go to work now.
两点
Snake eyes!
五点
Five!
双六
Boxcars!
五点
Five!
- 你是来开会的吗? - 什么?
- Are you in for the convention? - What?
你让我非常兴奋
You're making me really hot.
你好
Hello.
我或者在沙发躺几个小时 然后就走...
Perhaps I could crash on the couch for a few hours and then leave.
滚?
Get out.
收费多少?
I was wondering how much it would cost?
什么意思?
Sorry,guys.I don't know what you mean.
- 我只陪一个人 - 等一等 我们有钱
- Anyway,I only date one guy at a time. - Wait.We got money.
给她看
Show her the fucking money.
- 你们愿花多少? - 你要多少?
- How much are you willing to spend? - How much do you want?
1小时200元?
Two hundred for an hour?
- 你的朋友不说话? - 说啊
- Don't yourfriends talk? - Sure.
- 拍摄下来 - 微笑
- Get this on camera. - Smile.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 你好 - 好
- How you doin'? - I'm fine.
- 要喝点东西吗? - 别客气 钱呢?
- Do you want something to drink? - I'm fine.Where's the money?
钱
Money.
20 40 60 80 100
Twenty,40,60,80,a hundred.
- 把这拍下来 伙计 - 200块
- Get it on camera,dude. - Two hundred dollars.
- 好吧 谁先来? - 等一等
- All right,who's first? - Hold on a second.
吝啬鬼!他走出来时记得拍摄
Miser!You've gotta get him on camera when he comes out.
- 来 - 你俩先下楼
- Come on. - Look,you two go downstairs.
我要半小时
I'll be half an hour and then...
行 我们只想拍摄
The only thing is,we really wanna get him on tape.
这是他的初次 吝啬鬼 出来?
This is his first time.Come on,Miser!
我们只想看看
We just wanna see him.
哇!
Whoo!
- 问她吧 - 问她吧
- Ask her the question,man. - Come on,ask her.
- 我想干后门 - 不得干后门
- I wanna fuck you up the butt. - Nobody's doing any of that.
采取正常姿势 逐个来 做完我就走
You're all going straight,one at a time,and then I'm outta here.
- 听到没? - 再问
- You hear me? - Ask again.
- 干后门要多少钱? - 他又说了
- How much to fuck you up the butt? - He said it again!
- 我想干后门 - 干你的朋友的后门就好了
- I wanna fuck you up the butt. - Fuck one of your friends in the butt.
- 告辞 - 你说什么?
- I'm outta here. - Wait.What did she say?
- 你他妈的滚开? - 什么?
- Get out of my fuckin' way. - What did you say?Hold on.
- 我说 你他妈的滚开? - 别他妈的推我?
- Get the fuck out of my way! - Don't fuckin' push me!
你有什么问题?
What the fuck is your problem?
很对不起 大家冷静点?
Look,I'm really sorry,guys.Let's just calm down.
对不起 冷静点 对不起
I'm sorry.Just calm down.
- 操 吝啬鬼 - 妈的
- Fuck,Miser. - Shit.
- 妈的 - 操
- Shit. - Fuck.
去哪?
Where you headed?
维斯达421号
421 Vista.
我感觉你坐着有些不舒服
I couldn't help but notice you had a little trouble sittin' down.
遭人从后门乘虚而入?
You get a back door delivery you weren't expectin'?
有的士钱吗?
You gonna be able to pay for this?
我在问你 有的士钱吗?
I asked you a question.You got money?
- 没有就下车 - 我有钱
- I'll let you out here,sister. - I have money.
别向我出气
All right.Don't take it out on me.
我是防范被别人乘虚而入
I'm just covering my ass.
你大概也应学我
Somethin' maybe you should have thought about doing.
干她 吝啬鬼
Get her,Miser.
我来
Here,I got her.
你敢咬我?
Fuckin' bite me.
- 谁? - 范太太
- Who is it? - Mrs.Van Houten.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 对不起 本周末前请你搬出
Hi.I am sorry,but we have to ask you to be out by the end of the week.
全年旅馆
对不起 女士 他没搬回来
I'm sorry,ma'am.He hasn't checked back in.
什么事?罢工?
What is your problem?You're on strike?
出去?
Out.
什么问题嘛?
What's the problem?
问题是 我们不欢迎你
We don't want you in here.That's the problem.
来 我们走
Come on.Let's go.
放手 要走我自己会走
Let go of my arm.If you want me outta here...
- 我不想走 - 走吧
- I wanna be outta here. - You're going out.
下次不会客气
Next time it won't be so fuckin' easy.
恕我多口问一句 你发生了什么事?
It ain't none of my business,but what in the hell happened to you?
我...我跟人吵架了
I,uh...I had an argument.
一定吵得很厉害
Must have been a hell of an argument.
要是我 就甩掉他
If I was you,I'd leave him.
像你这样漂亮的小姐
A pretty young lady like you...
什么男人找不到 难道你不知道吗?
You can get any man you want.Don't you know that?
喂
Hello?
本
Ben?
本 你到底在哪儿?
Ben,where the fuck are you?
把地址给我
Give me the address.
本?
Ben?
本
Ben.
好暗
It's so dark in here.
你病得好厉害
You're so sick,
脸色多苍白
so pale.
我的爱人
My love.
你是我的爱人
You're my love.
需要人帮吗?
Do you want help?
需要我帮吗?
- Do you want my help? - No.
我只想见你
I want to see you.
你是我的天使
You're my angel.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
遇上点麻烦 但我没事
Something went wrong,but I'm OK.
对不起 我累人累己
I'm sorry I put us asunder.
不要紧
It's OK.
让我来
Let me do it.
来
There.There you go.
你令我多坚挺
See how hard you make me,angel?
你知道我爱你
You know I love you.
是的
Yeah.
我知道
I know.
我爱你
I love you.
我想其实是...
I think the thing is,
我们都意识到我们的时间不多了
we both realized that we didn't have that much time,
而且...
and...
我接受他 接受他的为人
...I accepted him for who he was.
没有希望他会改变
I didn't expect him to change.
而他对我也一样
I think he felt that for me,too.
我欣赏他的戏剧性
I liked his drama.
他需要我
And he needed me.
我爱他
I loved him.
我真心地爱他
I really loved him.